

About Me

I'm a meticulous front end web developer with over 2 years of experience in this sector. I'm passionate for building responsive websites and enjoy turning complex problems into simple, beautiful, and intuitive layouts.

Contact

+92 3302723502









mavia-ali.web.app

Karachi, Pakistan

maviaali597@gmail.com

Education

2019 - Present BS - Computer Science. Federal Urdu University of Arts, Sciences and Technology

2021

Microsoft Certified HTML & CSS Programmer

2016 - 2018

Inter. in Computer Science Aisha Bawani Govt College

2003 - 2016 Citizen's Public Secondary School

Mavia Ali

Front End Web Developer

Experience

FRONT END DEVELOPER | TEAM LEAD

Dynamic Global Links | April 2021 - Present

My job is to develop highly professional websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS and WordPress.

Lead and delegate tasks to the 4 members of front end team and provide counsel on all aspects of the projects

FRONT END DEVELOPER (INTERN)

Saylani IT House | 2019 - 2020

Completed internship at Saylani IT house during Web Development course.

Professional Skills



Interests

Cricket Coding **Exploring** Reading